Welcome to your first project.
欢迎来到你的第一个项目
Global temperature has been a hot topic in recent years,
全球气温是近年来的热门话题,
as politicians argue over climate change policy,
当政客们争论气候变化政策时,
and scientists try to understand how the world's climate is actually changing.
科学家们试图了解 世界气候实际上是如何变化的
Temperature data around the world is an important part of this conversation.
世界各地的温度数据是这个对话的重要组成部分
To measure temperature data,
为了测量温度数据,
scientists combine measurements from the air and ocean surface.
科学家综合了空气和海洋表面的测量数据
This data is collected by weather stations on land and in the ocean.
这些数据由陆地和海洋的气象站收集
In this project, you'll analyze local and global temperature data and
在这个项目中 您将分析本地和全球的温度数据
compare the temperature trends where you live to overall global temperature trends.
比较你居住地的气温趋势和全球气温趋势
You'll analyze the data, create a data visualization and write up your findings.
你将分析数据 创建一个数据可视化数据库 并写下你的发现 .最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6